{
    "subject": "Dominique_Deruddere",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Everybody's_Famous!",
    "human_readable": "Dominique Deruddere directed the film Everybody's Famous!",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8864228129386902,
            "question": "Is Dominique Deruddere a film director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8655999898910522,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Dominique Deruddere?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7422523498535156,
            "question": "What film did Dominique Deruddere direct?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7418720126152039,
            "question": "Is Everybody's Famous! a film directed by someone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7295119762420654,
            "question": "Who directed Everybody's Famous!?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6973121762275696,
            "question": "Who directed the film Everybody's Famous!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6695116758346558,
            "question": "Can you name a film directed by Dominique Deruddere?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5775373578071594,
            "question": "Does the name Dominique Deruddere appear in connection with filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4392094612121582,
            "question": "Name a filmmaker whose work includes Everybody's Famous!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39491668343544006,
            "question": "What type of work is associated with Dominique Deruddere?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dominique Deruddere directed the film Everybody's Famous!",
            "html": "yago_12877_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a filmmaker whose work includes Everybody's Famous!",
            "html": "yago_12877_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the name Dominique Deruddere appear in connection with filmmaking?",
            "html": "yago_12877_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a film directed by Dominique Deruddere?",
            "html": "yago_12877_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12877_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12877_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12877_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12877_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12877_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12877_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12877_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12877_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12877_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12877_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Dominique Deruddere directed the film Everybody's Famous. The documents mention that Deruddere is the writer-director of Everybody's Famous, and also mention it as one of his films, such as in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_12877/re-ranker-msmarco/49.txt where it says \"Everybody Famous\", which was indeed released worldwide...\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Dominique Deruddere, including that he directed the film \"Everybody's Famous,\" which was nominated for a foreign-language Oscar in 2001. This supports the triple stating that Dominique Deruddere directed the film \"Everybody's Famous.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}